> > 布莱恩: 我想和你一起建造的东西是一个导航栏。
&gt;&gt; Brian: The thing that I want
to build with you is a nav bar.
所以现在我们不像酒吧里的酒吧
So right now,
we don't have like a nav bar up here, but
我们要和一个叫做 " E运动" 的工具一起建造一个
we're gonna build one together
with a tool called Emotion.
现在，E运动是我们在 JS中称为 CSS 的一些东西。
Now, Emotion is something
that we would call CSS in JS,
这很有争议取决于你问谁
which is very controversial
depending on who you ask.
我认为，我认为 CSS 是很棒的，我很差劲。
I kind of reserve judgement that I
think CSS is great, and I'm bad at it.
但在 JS 里， CSS 是一个非常有趣的事情。
But CSS in JS I think is
a very interesting thing.
我认为E原议案是最具说服力的实施方式。
And I find Emotion to be the most
compelling implementation of it.
在之前的课程中我教了造型的组件
In previous versions of this course,
I taught styled components,
是另一个众所周知的
which is another well known one.
但如果你在这一点上， Ewon 差不多赢了，它的大部分都是
But if you, at this point, Emotion
pretty much has won, it has most of
它是最受欢迎的，最能表现的。
the developer mind share, it's the most
popular one, it's the most performant one.
所以，这绝对是一个，你应该考虑使用。
So, it's definitely one to,
you should probably think about using.
好吧这样我就能用 JavaScript 来做我所有的造型
Okay, so it allows me to do all
of my styling in JavaScript and
没有任何单独的 CSS 文件。
not have any separate CSS files.
但是它要做的就是把你的代码编译好
But what it will do is it
will compile your code so
会有一个独立的 CSS 文件对吧
that there will be a separate CSS file,
right?
你最后还是要和 JS 和 CSS 文件一起
So, you still end up with JS and
CSS files at the end, but
你的所有石刑都把它都加起来了
it mushes everything together for
all of your stylings as well.
所以我现在要你做的第一件事就是
So the first thing I
want you to do now is I'm
只会让我的服务器停停
gonna stop my server for just a second and
我要说 npm install @emotion/core
I'm gonna say npm install @emotion/core,
和 @emotion/babel - 预置-css-prop。
and @emotion/babel-preset-css-prop.
好的，这实际上是给我们一个核心库，它将会运行。
Okay, so this is actually going to give
us the core library that's going to run.
Eball 的运行时间为千字节，根本不是很大。
The runtime for Emotion is a couple of
kilobytes, it's not very big at all.
然后这个 babel - pre-prep -css - prep 让它做一些额外的编译
And then this babel-preset-css-prep allows
it to do some extra compiling ahead of
是时候让它更快了
time to make it even faster.
>> 布莱恩: 好的，我要回去做 npm 的工作了
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay,
i'm going to back to doing npm run dev so
我的服务器又启动了
that my server is started again.
然后我就把这个藏起来
And then I'm just going to hide this.
所以我想让你做个新文件
So I want you to make a new file.
我希望您将其称为 NavBar.js，在您的源目录中，并保存该目录。
I want you to call it NavBar.js, inside
of your source directory, and save that.
好了我们要从雷法进口
Okay, here we're going to
import React from React,
>> Brian: 从 @reach/router 导入链接，
&gt;&gt; Brian: import Link from @reach/router,
就像在一个锚上一样
which is gonna be a link,
as in a anchor tag.
我们将从 @emotion/core 导入 css 。
And we're going to import
css from @emotion/core.
>> Brian: 在这里，我们将说 const NavBar 等于一个函数。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Here we're going to say
const NavBar equals a function.
我们会在这里做一个隐含的回报。
And we'll do an implicit return here.
然后说标题， >> Brian: And
And say header,
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
然后联系到这个就像一个 href，
then link to, this is just like an href,
通过我，这将是徽标。
Adopt Me, this will be the logo.
然后在那下面
And then underneath that,
我们将会有一个带有伊斯兰教标识标签的跨距
we're going to have a span
with an aria label of logo.
然后我们要在这里放一个情绪激动的
And then we're going to
put an emoji in here.
然而你却选择在那里放上一个情绪
So however you choose to
put an emoji in there.
所以在 Mac上，您可以按下 Ctrl+Cmd+space 和
So in on Mac,
you can hit Ctrl+Cmd+space and
这将打开用于扇情的选择器。
this will open the selector for emojis.
你可以为这个项目挑选你最喜欢的标志。
And you can pick your favorite logo for
the project.
我肯定会和一个蠢货一起去的
I'm definitely gonna go with a poodle.
> > 布莱恩: 我也要给它一个角色。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
I have to give it a role as well.
so role = img.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，然后在下面
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and
then down here at the bottom
你会说出口默认的纳夫巴尔
you're gonna say export default NavBar.
那么到目前为止还没有什么特别的东西吗
So nothing special here too far,
right, so far?
但我想用这个标题做一些很酷的事情。
But I want to do something
cool with this header.
我要说 " css="
Here, I'm gonna say css=.
然后我就给它一个小 css
And then I'm gonna give it a css,
like that.
然后我就把它放在这儿
And then I'm gonna put a back tick here.
>> Brian: 因此，请注意，这是 css ，然后直接后是后退。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So notice that this is css, and
then directly afterward is a back tick.
现在我意识到这对我们大多数人来说都很奇怪因为我们大多数人
Now I recognize that this looks odd for
most of us, because most of us don't deal
在每天的 JavaScript中使用标记的模板字面值。
with tagged template literals
on a day to day in JavaScript.
这是 2015 年的一个特征，它是一个模板字符串，
This is a feature that came in in
2015 that it's a template string,
就像你能在这里的模板一样对吧
as in like a template string like
one that you could have here, right?
而且这也能起作用。
And this would work just as well.
就像这样对吧
Like that, right?
> > 布莱恩: 但它是有标记的，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian: But it's tagged, so
它将通过这个 CSS 函数运行它。
it's actually going to run it
through this CSS function.
这就是所有标记的模板字面值
So that's all a tagged
template literal does for
你是通过一个功能来运行这些东西的好吗
you is it runs this stuff
through a function, okay?
现在我们可以用普通的 CSS 来写。
Now we can write in here
in just normal CSS.
因此，背景色: #333。
So background-color: #333.
现在你们很多人可能没好
Now many of you are probably
not getting good
语法突出显示，对吧 ?
syntax highlighting right here, right?
注意我也要自动完成任务
And notice that I'm also
getting autocompletion.
所以如果我说立场的话，我也会在这里做得很好。
So if I say position, I'm getting
good autocompletion here as well.
所以我要告诉你们如何用代码来快速。
So I'm gonna show you how to do
that really quick with Code.
如果您单击此处的 " 扩展 " 部分。
If you click here on
the Extensions on the side.
搜索，以及
Search for, and
我意识到这有点反直觉，但也有一些成分。
I recognize this is a little
counterintuitive, but styled-components.
其实我已经装了
I actually have it already installed.
我来帮你找
So let me find it for you.
它是 vscode - styled-components，在这里。
It's vscode-styled-components,
this one here.
>> Brian: 因此安装此文件和
&gt;&gt; Brian: So install this one and
那么它就会神奇地解决你所有的问题
then it'll just magically
fix all of your problems.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，就按 vscosde-styled 搜索，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So yeah,
just search for vscode-styled,
可能是第一次了
it probably will be the first one.
在拍摄过程中，这有 47.5 万次下载，非常多。
So as of filming,
this has 475,000 downloads, so a lot.
> > 布莱恩: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay?
>> Brian: 因此，一旦您拥有此功能，就应该开始看到语法突出显示。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So once you have that, then you
should start seeing syntax highlighting.
您可能必须重新启动编辑器，但可能不是。
You might have to restart your editor,
but probably not.
也许吧
But maybe.
还有。
And.
> > 布莱恩: 那是
&gt;&gt; Brian: That's.
> > 布莱恩: 是的，我要给它 15 像素的填充物。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Yeah, so I'm gonna give
it padding of like 15 pixels.
是的，让我们看看这看起来是什么样的。
And yeah, let's see what that looks like.
> > 布莱恩: 所以我们得先把它放在首位，那是对的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So we have to go put
it in first, that's right.
所以我想让你去 app.js
So I want you to go into app.js.
这里有标题，让我们把它替换为标题。
And here we have the header,
let's just replace this with Header.
>> Brian: 或 NavBar，我们称之为 NavBar。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Or NavBar,
that's what we called it, NavBar.
> > 布莱恩: 我们也要进口。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
we'll have to import that as well.
>> Brian: 来自 ./NavBar。
&gt;&gt; Brian: From ./NavBar.
我们不再使用链接，因此您也可以将其删除。
And we stopped using links, so
you can go ahead and delete that as well.
从达图 / 路由器那里开始。
Up there from reach/router.
> > 布莱恩: 好吧，现在理论上
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so now in theory.
我想我们还有一件事要做
I think we have one more
thing to do here as well.
我们有
We do.
>> Brian: 所以我们安装了 Babel 预置。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
we installed the Babel preset.
所以我们最后需要做的事情是去照看婴儿，对不起，
So last thing we need to do here is
go into babble, sorry, .babelrc.
而且我们也要用这个
And we have to use this one as well.
所以
So
@emotion/bel-预置-css-prop
@emotion/babel-preset-css-prop
就像这样
like that.
所以你也要把这个也包括在内，
So you have to go include this as well,
因为巴贝尔也要为我们做一些转变
because babel has to do some
transformations for us as well.
你把这个情感/巴贝放进去了，所以
You put in this emotion/babel, so
我们实际上需要向它添加一个配置。
we actually need to add
one configuration to it.
在另一个阵列中换行。
So wrap this in another array.
在此处放置逗号，然后放置对象。
Put a comma here, and then an object.
你必须说 sourceMap: 假的。
And you have to say sourceMap: false.
>> 布莱恩: 这很烦人，因为你会失去做地图的能力。
&gt;&gt; Brian: It's annoying, because you're
gonna lose the ability to do source maps.
但是现在，E运动 CSS 道具与一些
But for right now, Emotion CSS
prop doesn't play well with some
还有其他的事情所以我们就得关闭地图
other things as well, so
we just have to turn off source maps.
在我看来，这并不是一个非常大的交易。
In my opinion,
it ends up not being a very big deal.
所以现在我们有了这么美丽的艺术作品
So now we get this beautiful work of
art that I'm probably killing our
设计师。
designer with.
但很漂亮我做了
But it's gorgeous and I made it.